A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council photographs FA101
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council photographs
1967-1978, undated
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council
FA101
1 Cubic Feet Extent is an estimate.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
File Plan note
P/1063
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists entirely of photographs.
Photographs
- Ektachrome Slides
  Scope and Contents note
  Sculpture, Carved objects, Art, ACC
- The Art of An Furuta
  Painting, Art, Exhibitions, ACC
- Leung Kui Ting
  Art, Exhibitions, ACC
- Rodolfo Samonte, 1972
  Art, Exhibitions,ACC
- Air Marshal H Budiardjo
  Indonesia, Wayang Museum
- Martha Graham Dance Company
  Dance, Theater, Art
- Wushu of China
  Dance, Art, Theater, ACC
- Cultural Center of the Philippines
  ACC, Museums, Exhibitions, Art
- Praphan Srisouta
  Art, Exhibitions
- Stanford University - Exhibition of Archaeological Finds from the PRC, Overall Condition: Good __1 __04/03/2000; Prints: 13 __0 __0 __0 __Collection on Deposit Negatives: 0 __0 __0 __0 __0 Other Formats: 0 __ __0
  Art, Archaeology, Exhibitions
- K. G. Subramanyan
  Painting, Art
- Toh Sugimora
  Architecture, Art, Exhibitions
- Salis Som, 1974
  Architectural Drawings
- Njoman Sumandhi, 1973
  Music, Art
- Hardja Susilo, 1977
  Theater, Art
- I Wayang Suweca, 1975
- Darius L. Swann, 1970
  Art, Masks
- John Szarkowski, 1971
  Art, Photography, Exhibitions
- Sadhiko Tachiki
  Candid
- Taman Ismail Marzurki
  Buildings
- Bo Gyllensvard - Chinese Art from the Collection of H. M. King, 1967
- AR Photos, 1978
- Shuya Abe, 1972
- Academy of American Poets Symposium, 1969